Immoral weapon?
That's right.
Your Heart Hybrid Gear contains...
...a hidden weapon called
an Immoral Weapon.
Once your Hybrid Count goes
above a certain level,
you'll probably be able to use it.
You should be able to get much
stronger than you are now.
Keep it up.
Deploying defensive utilities over
all of Ataraxia and Megafloat Japan.
Attention all students.
This is not a drill or a school event.
Everyone, this way!
This is a real battle!
Show these otherworld invaders
what you've learned!
We'll show them all the things
we've been working on!
Episode 4
Climax Hybrid
The enemy fleet is approaching
Ataraxia at high speed.
Fifty kilometers until
we're in main gun range.
Sis, why can't I launch?
Look.
Luck and fighting spirit won't
help us against those numbers.
Your time will come later.
Amaterasu is within range of
the enemy Magitech weapons.
Listen.
Your target is the enemy flagship,
the 2000-meter-long battleship.
Destroy it before its main cannon
can target Megafloat Japan!
Sheesh...
You make it sound so easy!
Here I come!
There!
Don't focus too much on the Magitech weapons!
Thirty kilometers until
we're in enemy battleship range.
Everyone...
I'm... number one!
A Dragorie...
Aine's Hybrid Count is
falling faster than usual.
If Chidorigafuchi's Count drops to zero...
Ten kilometers until
we're in enemy battleship range.
Chidorigafuchi.
This is...
...all I have!
Chidorigafuchi, you're overusing
your Absolute Zone!
I can defeat Category-A weapons, too.
I'm every bit as good as Yurishia and Hayuru.
You're overdoing it!
That took your Hybrid Count
all the way down to...
It's below ten percent!
That's plenty!
Wait, Chidorigafuchi!
Wait, Kizuna!
We're in range of the enemy battleship!
Just wait, Chidorigafuchi!
Eros!
I'm almost there...
But I'm out of energy.
Am I supposed to go that way?
Chidorigafuchi...
Chidorigafuchi!
Wake up!
Hida-kun...
Good, you're awake.
Where am I?
The tuning room in the Nayuta Labs.
You took a direct hit from the
enemy ship, but you're safe.
I think you were lucky.
Stay down.
What's the situation?
Their cannons have stopped firing,
but a drop squad of Magitech
weapons is landing now.
I need to get back out there...
Wait a second.
I can't send you out there, Chidorigafuchi.
Why?
I see.
My Hybrid Count is under five percent.
That means I can't even
equip my Heart Hybrid Gear.
Move.
I can't let you go out there to die.
I...
The Heart Hybrid Gear is all I have.
I'm not allowed to be
worse than anyone at using it!
And you're telling me I can't fight,
or even equip my Gear?
That means I'm worthless.
There's no reason for me to exist!
And there's no reason for me to live!
Chidorigafuchi...
I have nothing.
Absolutely nothing!
I don't know who I am or where I'm from.
I don't remember my name,
my home, or my family.
You're not surprised, huh?
That's right.
I was brought to this lab.
And after that,
I spent all my time as a test subject
in Dr. Nayuta's research.
I don't remember anything
before being brought here.
And all I remember after that
is being a guinea pig here.
That's all I have.
When I try to take an interest in something,
I start to wonder if the real me,
the old me, would've cared about it.
And once that starts,
I can't bring myself to care.
Once the combat tests started and I
came to the high school, it got worse.
You never thought about making friends?
I'm afraid to be around other people.
Because I never talked to anyone at the lab.
I'm incapable of holding a conversation.
But there is one thing I can lean on.
The Heart Hybrid Gear.
Whenever I got stronger,
Dr. Nayuta praised me.
She was happy.
I was the only one who could use
the Heart Hybrid Gear back then.
But outside of that,
there was nothing else I could do.
I'm better than anyone at
using the Heart Hybrid Gear,
and I'm stronger than anyone.
That's who I am!
But I can't defeat the enemy at all!
Hayuru's defeated 200 enemies. Yurishia, 300.
And I've only defeated thirty-eight.
Dr. Nayuta once told me...
...that there's an incredibly powerful
"Immoral Weapon" inside me.
When my Hybrid Count goes over its capacity,
it might appear, she said.
My mom said that?
I told myself that things would work out
if I got the Immoral Weapon.
But how could I get my Hybrid Count
above full when it just kept going down?
Just when I thought it might
be impossible after all,
you appeared, Kizuna Hida.
The man who can break the limits
on the Hybrid Count.
I was overjoyed.
I was filled with hope, and the
whole world seemed different.
You felt like a prince that
Dr. Nayuta had sent me.
I told myself I had to make you like me.
That I had to make you love me.
But I didn't know what to do.
I looked at everything I
could find in the database.
A magazine boys read...
...said that they liked it
when girls made them lunch.
But I couldn't cook,
so I didn't know what to do.
I made a lunch even though
I didn't know how to cook.
And then I read a naughty book for boys...
...to find out what would make you happy.
That's why you came to
wake me up that morning?
I-I was actually planning on doing
all sorts of things to wake you up.
B-But I couldn't.
And the other day...
I didn't know what you would do,
and I was scared...
But I thought it might get you
to make a move on me.
It didn't work, though.
I didn't get my Immoral Weapon.
In the end, I was useless.
There was no reason for me to even be alive.
Either way,
with that huge fleet out there,
Ataraxia might be finished.
Everyone's going to die, and it's my fault.
Enough!
What?
Worthless?
Useless?
You're just worried nobody's
telling you how great you are!
Don't act like you know anything!
So what if you can't beat someone?
So what if some people are better than you?
Don't throw a tantrum and put yourself down.
Shut up!
I don't want to be lectured by someone
who doesn't understand a thing!
Zeros!
Even if you think you don't have any talents,
and that you're nothing special,
try to figure out what you can do,
and how you can be of help.
That's the kind of outlook you need to have.
If you do, you'll find that everyone
in this world has a purpose!
Why didn't you dodge?
At least deploy your
Absolute Zone, you idiot.
You're right.
No way...
Let me see that.
The enemies hit me harder
than I thought they would.
You dummy! You dummy!
You fool! You useless dummy!
You're weak... You don't have any power...
So dodge!
Why did you do that for me,
when I can't even fight anymore?
All I can do now is die...
I helped my mom,
Nayuta Hida, with her research here.
But somebody who was better
for the research appeared,
and I was told I wasn't needed anymore.
I didn't know anything but the experiments,
but she threw me away anyway.
When I went on my own to the Tokyo Float,
and started going to school,
things were really bad.
Because I could barely even talk to anyone.
But...
A person's value isn't
decided by their abilities.
It's decided by how they live.
We can always go back and do things over.
We can always start over.
That's what I learned then.
But...
I don't know how to live.
Neither do I.
So let's think together
about how we can live.
Chidorigafuchi?
Kizuna, um...
Do a Heart Hybrid with me, would you?
I can start over, right?
It's embarrassing,
but I don't mind if it's with you.
Aine...
Take responsibility, okay?
Roger.
Don't play with my body...
Does it hurt?
It feels good.
You're so cute.
It worked, Aine.
Kizuna, I want more.
You haven't had enough yet either, right?
Hey, Kizuna...
My body feels hot.
Hurry up and take responsibility.
Wh-What's gotten into you, Aine?
Allow me to explain.
Shikina-san!
It's a side effect of the Heart Hybrid.
When the Heart Hybrid is successful,
the girl is overcome with strong
symptoms that resemble lust.
Their libido goes into overdrive.
That's a huge nuisance!
But if you can use that effect properly,
you can proceed to a higher stage.
A higher stage?
Yes, a new kind of Hybrid that
will allow for the acquisition...
...of Immoral Weapons.
The Climax Hybrid.
Hey, Aine, what are you...?
You're talking to another woman
when you should be having fun with me?
Th-That's not true, Aine.
You're all I'm thinking about right now.
Then prove it.
Hurry.
Aine...
Oh, Kizuna...
It feels so good, Kizuna...
Kizuna...
I-I can't breathe...
No! At this rate, I'm going to suffocate!
N-No!
Don't...
No!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Aine!
Aine-san!
Are you two okay?!
Yes.
You saved us!
You're going to pay for all this.
Pulverizer!
What's that?
Zeros's new weapon?
Connect!
The Climax Hybrid succeeded, didn't it?
That is her Immoral Weapon.
Now it's our turn.
Charge!
I can buy you time to blast that thing.
Zeros Mode!
That's Eros?
It seems as fast and powerful as the Zeros!
Take this!
Blast!
Enemy battleship has
disappeared from the radar!
The enemy fleet has withdrawn
beyond firing range.
We've won!
Yay!
Hooray!
Why are you standing out here,
looking so glum?
What about you? Did you enjoy the party?
I'm tired after being
dragged around everywhere.
I see.
Hey, Kizuna.
I got something else
besides my Immoral Weapon...
...when I did my Climax Hybrid.
What was that?
A fragment of my memories.
What?
A beautiful lake, and snow-covered peaks.
A huge city with tall buildings.
And a huge, complicated mechanical
clock that covered a whole wall.
That's great!
So I want you to do it again—
Ah! There you are!
What are you two doing?!
If it isn't the Japanese and American aces,
who couldn't shoot down a
single enemy battleship!
I don't want to hear that from
the first girl to get shot down.
That's right.
You were the one who...
Did you know?
Know what?
I got in trouble deliberately.
You don't want to stop them, Captain?
I probably should.
Why the sudden call?
Reiri, take a look at this.
A human?
And they're wearing what looks
like a Heart Hybrid Gear.
What's a human doing with the
Magitech weapons from another world?
Are they from that other world as well?
Found you!
Illustration: Choboraunyopomi
Did something happen between Kizuna and Aine?
It sure looks like it.
I'll have to go after him hard, too.
Next time: Beauty of the Land of Rubble
The "Love Room?"
What's that?